-You are very good on tarot cards.
-It's not a bad idea at all.
In the future, I think it will be more common with journalists-
-Or focusing on areas they know well and receives revenue directly from the reader.
It becomes important for us consumers to be critically set-
-And critically consume this type of independent journalists.
Is this reporter an expert, credible or bought?
Is it sponsored?
We have to get better at seeing it.
A world grows where both you and your readers can fit.
It becomes more important how journalists act.
Are they professional?
Do they stick to facts without personal opinions coloring the reports?
Can they correct?
Are they purchased?